http://www.marywood.edu/policy/detail.html?id=95121&crumbTrail=Website%20Privacy%20Policy&pageTitle=Policies%20and%20Procedures%20Manual:%20Website%20Privacy%20Policy

Policy Statement
Marywood University respects the privacy of users of its website. For those who access the site for information purposes, the University stores only anonymous data related to one's use of the site. This information helps to provide the best quality information and the kind of online offerings desired by users.
Information collected through forms and other online services connected to the Marywood University Website is private and confidential. Use of this information is governed by the University’s Family Educational Rights and Privacy Policy (based on FERPA) and applicable federal and state laws. Responses to questions regarding race, sex, sexual orientation, gender identity, color, national or ethnic origin, age, creed, ancestry, religion, disability, or any other legally protected status are voluntary, are kept confidential, and are not used to deny access for admission, employment, and/or services. They are, however, used to assist the University in providing data to demonstrate compliance with federal regulations.
Marywood’s website contains links to other sites. Marywood is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of other such sites. Marywood encourages its users to exercise caution when leaving the Marywood site for another site and to read carefully the privacy statements of any site that collects personally identifiable information.
Social Security numbers are requested on applications for admission and employment. They are used for identification when required for certain matters, e.g., those relating to federal and state financial aid, employment background checks, and tax reporting. Access to social security numbers is restricted only to staff members who need them to provide services.
Procedures
Questions about this Website Privacy Policy, the practices of the site, or dealings with the website should be referred to the Director of Web Development.
Related Policies
Code of Conduct
Conditions of Computer Use
Institutional Property Policy
Intellectual Property Policy
Social Media Policy
Related Committees
Technology Advisory Committee (TAC)
History
05/04/01 - Approved by the President as recommended by the Policy Committee of the University 04/20/05 - Revision of paragraph relating to social security numbers approved by the President of the University05/06/10 - Title change from Marywood University Webmaster to Director of Web Development.10/12/11 - Revision approved by the President of the University as recommended by the Policy Committee of the University.03/08/19 – Revisions approved by the President of the University as recommended by the Policy Committee of the University.
Secretary of the University & General Counsel
|
103
Immaculata Hall
570-340-6018
| F: 570-340-6014
| paterson@marywood.edu
Please note, the materials presented on this website are provided for informational purposes only and may not be construed as legal advice from the Office of the Secretary of the University and General Counsel.
2300 Adams Avenue Scranton, PA 18509
570-348-6211
| toll free: 1-TO-MARYWOOD
Sponsored by Sisters, Servants of Immaculate Heart of Mary
Privacy Policy
|
Web Accessibility
|
Future Students ApplyingMajorsOrientationActivitiesFinancial Aid
Alumni Alumni EventsReconnectGet InvolvedGive to Marywood
News Marywood NewsThis WeekMagazineEventsThe Wood WordGalleries
Resources Parking & MapsJobsBookstorePoliciesMission & Goals
